[
  {
    "question": "The female external genitalia include mons pubis, labia majora, labia minora, ______ and clitoris.",
    "answer": "hymen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mons pubis is a cushion of ______ tissue covered by skin and pubic hair.",
    "answer": "fatty"
  },
  {
    "question": "The labia majora are ______ folds of tissue, which extend down from the mons pubis and surround the vaginal opening.",
    "answer": "fleshy"
  },
  {
    "question": "The labia minora are ______ folds of tissue under the labia majora.",
    "answer": "paired"
  },
  {
    "question": "The opening of the vagina is often covered partially by a membrane called ______.",
    "answer": "hymen"
  },
  {
    "question": "The clitoris is a tiny ______-like structure which lies at the upper junction of the two labia minora above the urethral opening.",
    "answer": "finger"
  },
  {
    "question": "The hymen is often torn during the first ______.",
    "answer": "coitus"
  },
  {
    "question": "The hymen can also be broken by a sudden fall or ______.",
    "answer": "jolt"
  },
  {
    "question": "In some women the hymen ______ even after coitus.",
    "answer": "persists"
  },
  {
    "question": "The presence or absence of ______ is not a reliable indicator of virginity or sexual experience.",
    "answer": "hymen"
  },
  {
    "question": "A functional ______ gland is characteristic of all female mammals.",
    "answer": "mammary"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mammary glands are paired structures (______) that contain glandular tissue and variable amount of fat.",
    "answer": "breasts"
  },
  {
    "question": "The glandular tissue of each breast is divided into 15-20 mammary ______ containing clusters of cells called alveoli.",
    "answer": "lobes"
  },
  {
    "question": "The glandular tissue of each breast is divided into 15-20 mammary lobes containing clusters of cells called ______.",
    "answer": "alveoli"
  },
  {
    "question": "The cells of alveoli secrete ______, which is stored in the cavities (lumens) of alveoli.",
    "answer": "milk"
  },
  {
    "question": "The alveoli open into mammary ______.",
    "answer": "tubules"
  },
  {
    "question": "The tubules of each lobe join to form a mammary ______.",
    "answer": "duct"
  },
  {
    "question": "Several mammary ducts join to form a wider mammary ______ which is connected to lactiferous duct.",
    "answer": "ampulla"
  },
  {
    "question": "The mammary ampulla is connected to lactiferous duct and opens at the ______.",
    "answer": "nipple"
  },
  {
    "question": "Milk is expressed during ______.",
    "answer": "breastfeeding"
  }
]
